简 这早午餐真绝了
Jane, this brunch is amazing.
哦 有么 我只是看了一些烹饪博客
Oh, please. I was just reading some cooking blogs
又参考了美食网站然后就 嗯
and got a little epicurious and decided to just, you know,
把东西乱七八糟地一煮 来点核桃糖?
throw together whatever looked fun. Candied walnut?
真的太好吃了 全是你自己做的?
These are fantastic. Did you make 'em yourself?
简单的不能再简单了
Couldn't have been easier.
你只需敲开 弄个小孔 烤一下
You just crack 'em, hole 'em, toast 'em,
再用橄榄油那么一抹
brush 'em with a little bit of olive oil,
然后把他们和辣椒粉姜粉
then rub 'em with cayenne pepper, some turmeric
肉桂糖一起搅拌 放进烤箱
and some cinnamon sugar, and you put 'em in the oven
快速烘烤 每五分钟翻一次
for a quick roast, flipping them every five minutes
总共一个半小时 -我说你这是要飙泪么?
for... an hour and a half. - Are you crying?
有点 我快累死了
A little bit. I am just so tired.
伙计们 我不想总是成为
Guys, I hate to be the girl that, like,
大家谈话的焦点
makes every conversation about her,
但说实话 -你就是
but let's be honest. - You are.
是滴 我今天晚上要去相亲
Yeah, I am. I'm going on a blind date tonight
对方是听起来超赞的的 罗杰
with the most amah-zing sounding guy, Roger.
现在还有人叫罗杰?
Are people still named Roger?
你得把这个推了 今天晚上你和我一起出去
You gotta cancel it. You have a date tonight with me.
我爸妈来了
My parents are in town.
你都做了我三年的女朋友了
You're my girlfriend of three years.
晕 我把他们进城这事忘得一干二净
Oh, my God. I totally forgot they were coming.
对不起 我不能再做你的假女友了
I'm so sorry. I can't be your beard.
你是说去跟陌生人约会来得
You're telling me that one single date with some stranger
比咱俩之间虚假的感情更重要?
is more important to you than what we fake have?
是啊 而且说实话 我再不想做你的挡箭牌了
Yeah, and honestly, I'm sick of being your beard.
虽然你完全不像个同志
I mean, for someone who behaves nothing like a gay guy,
但你装直男装的也太不像了吧
you have even less of an idea how to act like a straight guy.
看看这一对 怎么样?真是无限享受啊
How about these things, huh? Can't get enough of these.
我说的对吧?耶!
Am I right? Yeah!
然后你又接着说"更别说这块地方里的乐事了
And then you followed it with "and don't even get me started
-那我怎么办?
"with what's going on down there." - So what am I gonna do?
也许你应该勇敢出柜
Maybe you should come out.
呃 出柜这种行为太GAY了，再说也没必要
Ugh. Coming out is so gay. And why should I?
我爸妈两年才来一次
My parents only visit, like, once every two years.
嘿 我可以做你的假女友哦 但我要叫拉丽莎
Hey, wait. I can be your beard, but I wanna be named Larissa,
而且我要做个雕刻家 -简 你能帮我不?
and I'm a... Sculptress. - Jane, will you do it?
为什么找我? -为什么不找我?
Why me? - Why not me?
拜托了 你是我唯一的希望 -我说我可以啊
Please, you're my only hope. - I just offered.
简 其他人都帮不了我了
Jane, there is no one else that can do this.
喂 为啥没人理我?当我不存在? -是滴
Wait. Can nobody hear me? Am I ghost? - Yes.
不是针对你 我只是觉得
It's nothing personal. I just personally feel
简会做的更好 -这还不叫针对我?
that Jane would be better at it. - How is that not personal?
这倒是，扮同志的女友我绝对一流的
It's true. I'd be an awesome beard.
父母们都喜欢我 -那么你答应了?
Parents love me. - So you'll do it.
不 马科斯 是时候你该向他们出柜了
No, Max. It's time for you to come out.
简说的对 -好了，我知道你们啥意思了
Jane's right. - Look, I hear you guys.
阿莱克斯 你帮我不?
Alex, will you do it?
没门！我都说了三遍了你却当面羞辱了我
No! I offered three times and you insulted me to my face.
那是因为我以为我可以找到更好的人选啊
It's only 'cause I thought I had someone better.
我是说...
I mean...
幸福终点站
第一季  第04集
==深影字幕组==
真不知道在七点之前我该去哪找个完美的女孩
So I don't know where I'm gonna find a perfect girl
当挡箭牌 -嘿 我有个疯狂的想法
to play a beard by 7:00. - Hey, I got a crazy thought.
你想穿裙子抹口红化身成性感兔女郎?
Put you in a dress and lipstick like sexy bugs bunny?
你个傻逼
Idiot.
对你的父母出柜吧 不会太糟糕的
Come out to your parents. It won't be that bad.
他们是和蔼开明的犹太人
They're sweet liberal Jews.
首先 你根本不知道他们会如何反应
First of all, you never know how they're gonna react.
其次 他们超想抱孙子
Second of all, they're obsessed with grandkids.
要是我告诉他们 我没法要孩子
How bad are they gonna freak when I tell 'em
他们一定会崩溃 -你还是可以有孩子啊
I can't have kids? - You can still have kids.
呃! 我才不想要孩子
Ugh! I don't want kids.
马科斯 这都是借口 知道不?
Max, these are just excuses. All right?
我知道这有点困难
I know it's hard, but come on.
但是 兄弟 今天晚上你真的应该坦白了
You should tell 'em tonight.
我跟你一起去 给你精神支持 -真的?
I'll come with you for moral support. - You'd do that for me?
当然了 兄弟 因为我爱你啊
Of course I would, buddy, 'cause I love ya.
其实是因为你知道我爸会买单吧
Plus you know my dad's gonna pay for dinner.
没错 我要两道开胃菜 估计还能再吃个牛排
Yeah, I'm gonna get two apps and probably a steak.
还有蟹肉土豆泥 -我就喜欢蟹肉土豆泥
Yeah, crab mashed potatoes. - Love me some crab mash-up.
难以置信 我花了3小时
Unbelievable. I spent three hours,
却没人注意到我精心用餐巾环套好的餐巾
and nobody even noticed the homemade napkin rings
还是荷叶边的 -我注意到了
made from rickrack. - I noticed.
真的?指给我看看?
Really? Can you point to them on this table?
何必呢?
Why you gotta do that?
不给马科斯当挡箭牌是不是有点不够意思?
Was it wrong that I didn't wanna be Max's beard?
我只是觉得向父母出柜的话
I just think he'd be so much happier
他会更快乐
if he were honest with his parents.
必须的，好奇的问一句
Yeah, totally. Just curious. Didn't it take you,
你是不是也用了半年时间才告诉你父母
like, six months, before you told your parents
你和一个黑人住一起? -这根种族没有关系
you were living with a black guy? - That had nothing to do with race.
我父母不在乎肤色
My parents don't see color.
他们只关心的是谁睡了他们的女儿
They just see sleeping with their daughter.
噢 我可不仅仅是睡觉而已
Oh, I sleep the sleep out of that.
我知道 总之 我需要在自己准备好的时候
I know you do. Anyway, I just needed to tell them
再告诉他们 -可是马科斯
in my own time. - As opposed to Max,
今晚就要向父母说真话
who has to tell his parents he's gay tonight
因为他的异性恋朋友认为他应该这么做?
because his straight friends think he should?
那不一样 -怎么不一样?
No, that is totally different. - How?
你何必呢?
Why you gotta do that?
不好意思 请问你是莎拉么?
Excuse me. Are you Sarah?
不是 我猜你不是罗杰
No. Oh. And I'm guessing you're not Roger.
现在说是的话是不是有点晚?
Is it too late to say that I am?
那现在说"鸡蛋要半生的还是全熟"（指早餐）是否有点早?
Is it too early to say, "how do you like your eggs?"
抱歉 我一紧张
I'm sorry. Oh, when I get nervous,
就变身成"黄金女郎"里的布兰奇
I turn into Blanche from "The Golden Girls."
那我就是剧中的索菲亚了
I'm a Sophia man myself.
哦 -我是道格
Oh. - I'm Doug.
我是彭妮 那么你也在等着相亲咯?
Hi. Penny. Uh, so you're waiting for a blind date, too?
是啊 可是我都等了半个多小时了
I was, but I've been here, like, a half an hour.
我想我被放鸽子了 - 彭妮?彭妮 哈茨?
I think I've been stood up. - Penny? Penny Hartz?
彭妮 哈茨?
Penny Hartz?
我猜我也被人放了鸽子...
And it looks like I've been stood up, too, so...
你不打算给他一个机会?
Did you wanna give him another minute?
不 -你确定?
I'm good. - You sure?
确定 -好吧 要喝的么?
Yeah. - Okay. You want a drink?
好啊 谢谢 -不客气
Yes, please. - All right.
好的
Okay.
嗨 马科斯! 马科斯!
Oh, Max! Maxie!
嘿 马科斯 我们在这
Hey, Max. We're here.
在这 -看见我们没?
Over here? - You see us?
我们在这! -他们没来 咱撤吧
We're here! - No, they're not here. Let's go.
嘿 没事的
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
像个爷儿们一样告诉他们你喜欢爷儿们
Now man up and tell 'em you like dudes.
快过来!
Get over here now!
嘿 妈妈
Hey, mom.
嗨 宝贝 -嘿
Hello, sweetheart. - Hey, hey.
嘿 亲爱的 -很高兴见到你
Hi, honey. - Good to see ya.
- 你穿的够暖吗? - 是的 我够暖和了
Are you warm enough? - Yes, I'm warm enough.
嘿 老爹 你还好么?
Hi, dad. How are you?
哦 戴夫也来了 戴夫 真是个惊喜
Oh, and Dave, too. Mwah! Dave, this is such a nice surprise.
彭妮呢?我们可是急着见她呢
Where's Penny? We were so excited to see her.
哦 她来不了了
Oh, she couldn't make it.
为什么?
Why?
她很忙 -他们分手了
She's busy. - They broke up.
到底是很忙还是分手了?
Well, which is it... busy? Broke up?
哦 这家伙依旧对分手这种事
Ooh, you know, breakups are still a bit
敏感呢 -戴夫 亲爱的 你想谈谈么?
of a hot-button issue for this guy. - Dave, honey, do you wanna talk about it?
事实上 马科斯才是那个...
Actually, Max is the one who really...
因为马科斯告诉我们
'cause from what Max has told us,
那个叫阿莱克斯的女生把你给甩了...
that Alex girl leaving you... that was the best thing
这事儿真的再好不过了 -我一直都这么说啊
that could have happened. - That's what I've been saying.
现在你终于可以做回自己了 -是啊
Now you're free to be who you are. - Exactly.
然后在男人的怀抱中找到幸福
And find happiness with men.
是啊!等等 这和男人有什么关系?
Yes! Wait. What's that with the men thing?
能给我俩几秒钟么?
Could you give us a quick second?
我得再要一杯
I'm gonna order one more drink.
快速提示，我父母认为你是同志 -什么?
Quick sidebar... my parents think you're gay. -What?
而且是超级GAY的那种 -为什么?
Like, super gay. - Why?
elle degenerous是美国著名的脱口秀主持人，是拉拉，发型和DAVE的有点像
可能是因为你的elle头 ，好吧，上大学的时候我父母
Maybe the Ellen haircut. Look, in college, my parents found
发现了我床垫下面的钙片 我慌了
my porn underneath my mattress, and I panicked.
然后我就说是你的
I said it was yours.
我的毛片怎么会跑到你的床垫下面?
Why would my porn be under your mattress?
我又慌了，就说你有次躺在我床上
I panicked again, and I said that you used to lie in my bed
而且超级迷恋我 -你抗压能力实在太差
and were obsessed with me. - You are not good under pressure.
你以为我不知道? -我们要立刻把这事彻底澄清
Don't you think I know that? - We are clearing this up once and for all.
霍华德 葆琳 马科斯有话要说
Howard, Pauline, Max has something
他憋了很久了
he's been meaning to tell you for a long, long time.
额...这个说起来有点难为情
Uh... this is, uh, kinda tough to say,
恩 戴夫是同志
but, um, Dave's gay.
哦 亲爱的 我们早就知道了
Oh, honey, we knew that.
是啊 很明显
Yeah, it's pretty obvious.
马科斯
Max.
我之所以和彭妮分手是因为...
The reason I'm not dating Penny anymore is 'cause...
我 嗯...
I'm, um...
嘿 亲亲，很抱歉我来迟了 嗨
Hey, boo! So sorry I'm late. Hi.
嗨 -我的现任女友是简
Hi. - I'm dating Jane now.
啊 -额?
Ah. - Hmm?
瞧瞧这一对 怎么样?
Get a load of these. Huh?
我就是喜欢...大波波 -真的?
I love... lady parts. - Do you?
真的
Yes.
真不相信我们现在才认识
I can't believe we just met.
跟你聊感觉很舒服 -你也是
You're so easy to talk to. - You, too.
通常第一次约会我都会感觉压力超大
And usually on first dates, I feel so much pressure
因为要装成一个博览群书的人
to pretend I read.
真的 看书最讨厌了
I know. I hate reading.
哎 -您的账单
Ugh. - Here you go.
我请客 -你真贴心
Oh, no, let me get this. - So sweet.
彭妮?
Penny?
彭妮 哈茨?
Penny Hartz?
彭妮
Penny.
嘿 明天晚上可以请你吃饭么?
Hey. Can I take you to dinner tomorrow night?
这个酒吧挺适合相亲
This bar's fine for a blind date,
不过你值得去更好的地方
but you deserve to be taken somewhere exceptional.
喔 你怎么可能还是单身?
Wow. How are you still single?
我也想问你同样的问题呢
I could ask the same thing about you.
失陪一下
Excuse me for a second.
喔 黑卡 你是在积分消费么
Oh, black card. Are you enjoying your reward points,
那个...
mister...
"希特勒"?
"Hitler"?
爸 妈 你们终于有机会见到我的新女友了
Mom, dad, I'm so happy you get to meet my new girlfriend,
亲爱的 真高兴你及时赶到了
and, honey, so glad you got to make it.
我去搬个椅子 -我去帮你 简?
I am gonna grab a chair. - I'll help you with that chair. Jane?
你不帮忙搬自己的椅子么?
So... You don't wanna help with your own chair?
好吧
Hi.
那椅子一定很重啊 -是啊
That must be quite a chair. - Yeah.
你来这干什么?
What are you doing here?
我以为我们都同意马科斯今晚要出柜的
I thought we agreed Max is gonna come out tonight.
我想了想
I thought about it,
如果他还没准备好 我们决定了也没用
and I decided it is not up to us to push him if he is not ready.
所有你准备让他一直这么撒谎?太逊了
So you're gonna let him live a lie? That sucks.
嘿！别和我女朋友那么讲话
Hey! You don't talk to my girlfriend like that!
简 如果你真要这么做
Listen, Jane, if you're gonna do this,
你得了解好多背景故事
there's a lot of backstory that you need to know.
别担心，都是小菜一碟
Don't worry. I am gonna crush this.
我就是迷惑家长的海洛因，好吗?
I am parent heroin, okay?
葆琳  霍华德真开心终于见到你们了
Pauline, Howard, it is so great to finally meet you.
我有一个绝妙的周末计划
I have an awesome weekend planned.
葆琳 明天早上 你和我折扣店见
Pauline, tomorrow morning, you, me, outlet malls,
中午 霍华德和我去打高尔夫
and then at noon, Howard and I are gonna tee off, and bring
记得带钱包哦 我可不会帮你省钱哦
your wallet, 'cause I am not gonna go easy on you, okay?
真的?行啊 不过你不忙么?
Really? That is so great. You're not too busy?
不忙的 为我心爱男人的父母
No, I would do anything for the two people
我愿意做任何事
that made this guy possible.
是吧 亲爱的? -是的
Right, honey? - Yeah.
过来 -什么?
Come here. - What?
过来 -好吧
Come here. Mm. - Okay.
戴夫 别嫉妒
Dave, don't be jealous.
你会遇到你的白马王子
You'll meet your knight in shining armor.
我可没嫉妒  因为我不是同志
I'm not jealous, 'cause I'm not gay.
好了 两杯苏格兰威士忌 这是你的水果汁
Okay, two scotches, ahd here's your daiquiri.
有没有搞错，伙计你来的也太准时了吧
Really, guy, that's your timing?
你知道 那真是个有趣的名字 海特勒
You know, that's an interesting name... Hyte-ler
是 希特勒
It's Hitler.
噢 不是发 "海特勒" 吗?
Oh, it's not pronounced "hyte-ler"?
- 不是 - 可能吗?
- No. - Could it be?
这种情况经常发生
This always happens.
每次女孩们听到我的名字 她们都会这么想
Whenever girls hear my name, all they can think is,
"他和希特勒是亲戚吗?"
"Is he related to that Hitler?"
我可不这么想 不过你是吗?
I am not thinking that. Are you?
不 当然没关系 一点关系都没有
No, of course not. There's no relation at all.
你的家族没有想过改名字吗?
And your family never considered changing the name?
好吧 这么说吧
Okay, here it is.
在美国 希特勒这个名字已经存在200年了
The American Hitlers came to this country 200 years ago.
我们可是原住民
We were regular solid citizens.
我的堂兄 罗恩 希特勒 拥有中东第二大的
My cousin, Ron Hitler, owns the second largest
床垫产业链
mattress chain in the midwest.
他卖了很多mein kampforters吗 （彭妮以为是德语床垫）
Does he sell a lot of "mein kampforters"?
说的不错，听着，你看上去好极了，我发誓
That's good. Look, you seem great, and I swear,
我很正常 所以我们可以回到你只是 彭妮
I am normal, so can we go back to when you were just Penny,
而我只是 道格  一个希望可以在
and I was just Doug, a guy hoping that you'd have
明晚与你共度晚餐的人?
dinner with him tomorrow night?
当然 我很乐意与你共度晚餐
Yes, yes, I would love to have dinner with you,
道格 希... 道格
Doug Hi... Doug.
还需要时间适应 哈?
Takes some getting used to, huh?
呃 我想是的
Yes. Yes, it does.
那么
So...
他们很喜欢我
They loved me.
我知道他们会的
Knew they would.
我是说 我一点都不惊讶
I mean, I'm not surprised.
我很风趣 热情 深情
I was funny, warm, affectionate.
那很不错 宝贝
That's great, babe.
- 有多深情? - 噢 你知道 牵牵手
- How affectionate? - Oh, you know, we held hands,
碰碰鼻子 亲了几次 - 你亲了 马科斯?
some light nuzzling, kissed once or twice. - You kissed Max?
呃 我必须的那么做
Well, I had to sell it.
我是说 我已经是离弦的箭了
I mean, I was on fire.
我的意思是 我与一些犹太人一起
I mean, I worked in some yiddish,
- 讨论一点高尔夫 - 舌吻吗?
- a little golf talk... - was there tongue?
你怎么这么奇怪? 他是个同志
Why are you being so weird about this? He's gay.
他现在还是吗? 这看上去很方便
Is he now? Seems convenient.
这件事让你很烦恼吗?
Is this really bothering you?
不 不怎么嫉妒 我知道我才是你的唯一亲亲
No. Not really jealous. I know I'm your only boo-boo.
噢
Oh.
嘿 亲亲 是 马科斯 怎么样了?
Hey, boo. It's Max. So?
你干得很不错
You nailed it.
耶! 我就知道! 我就知道!
Yes! I knew it! I knew it!
我可是家长杀手
I'm parent heroin.
他们已经爱上 简了 而那很不好
They have got a Jane addiction, and it's bad.
我是说 "在公车站摇晃 还愿意为我
I'm talking "shaking at a bus stop, willing to do
拿包的" 那种
downstairs stuff for a nickle bag of me" bad.
所以我明早 9 点来接伯母 或者
So should I pick your mom up at 9:00 tomorrow, or...
我给你打电话就是因为这个
That's kinda what I was calling about.
呃 我爸爸生意上有些急事
You see, my dad has this business thing that came up,
他们要坐早上 6 点的飞机回去
and they're on, like, a 6:00 A.M. flight.
- 呃 那真糟糕 - 是的 他们也很不爽
- Oh, that's too bad. - Yeah, they're bummed.
但你今天的表现巨赞
But operation beard was a huge success.
我欠你一个大人情
I owe you big-time.
要是你什么时候想去乡村俱乐部
If you ever wanna get into a country club
本集结尾部分的内容
需要一个假的白人丈夫
and you're looking for, like, a fake white husband,
我随时恭候
I'm your guy.
他们明天一大早就走
They're leaving early.
天 我还很期待与他们一起逛逛
God, I was so looking forward to hanging out with them.
噢
Oh.
不要 我觉得你现在很脏
No. Feels dirty now.
我昨晚度过了一个最诡异的约会
I had the weirdest date last night.
好吧 我昨晚和马科斯
Okay, I made out with Max
在他父母面前亲热了一番
in front of his parents last night,
所以你的约会不可能比我的还诡异
so you might not wanna play weird date poker with me.
你还是决定去了? 怎么样?
You decided to go? How was it?
搞定了 他们爱死我了 但他们很早就得走
Nailed it. They loved me. They had to leave early,
不过 马科斯 说他们因为不能
but Max said they were devastated
和我多呆下而痛苦的要死
they didn't get to spend more time with me.
是吗? 在我看来他们可好的很哪
Really? 'Cause they look like they're doing okay to me.
噢 呃 我
Oh, uh... I...
你好 马科斯
Hello, Max.
我的亲娘啊
不好意思 我吓着你了吗?
I'm sorry. Did I startle you?
你不用道歉
You're not sorry.
你一个人坐在我的公寓里还不开灯
You're sitting alone in my apartment in the dark.
- 我很确定你是故意那么做 - 我过来
- Pretty sure you meant to do that. - I just wanted to come by,
只是想确定你父母走了没
make sure your parents got off okay.
噢 那很不错 很好
Yeah. It's great. Fine.
你确定吗? 在机场没排什么长长的队伍?
You sure? No long lines at the terminal?
没晚点吗?
No delays?
没有啊 你知道 都很顺利
No, it was smooth. You know...
噢 很好
Oh, good.
十分非常以及特别好 不过要在爱玛店吃早餐
Good, good, good, 'cause there can be such a long wait
可要排很久队的吧
for a table at Emma's.
是啊，自从那次被大众点评推荐之后
Yeah, well, since that review came out, you know, and...
好吧 他们还在这
All right, fine. They're still here.
而且今晚才走
They're not leaving till tonight.
那你为什么给我说他们走了?
Why did you tell me they were leaving?
他们喜欢我 - 呃
They loved me. - Uh...
他们不喜欢我?
They didn't love me?
- 恩 - 但我绝对把他们拿下了啊
- Uh... - But I killed.
我想你不懂这词在这种情况下
I don't think you understand what "killed" means
的含义
in this context.
有一晚  马科斯 和我第一次吵架
So the other night, Maxie and I got in our first fight,
我试着对他发火 但你们看他
and I tried to stay mad at him, but look at this punim.
怎么可能会对这张帅脸发火啊?
How could you stay mad at this punim?
是啊 怎么会?
- How could ya?
噢 让姐亲一下这张帅脸
Ooh, give me this punim.
哦
Oh.
但是你们知道，都是从这位先生这里遗传过来的
But you know. You know, since he gets it from this guy.
哈? 噢 看看你
Huh? Ooh, look at you.
噢 我得去上个厕所
Oh. This shiksa's gotta pish.
她还学了犹太语啊
She's even learning yiddish.
天啊，她可真是啥都会
Boy, she's a keeper.
- 是的 我是 - 我知道 知道
- Yes, I am. - I know, I know, I know.
我真受不了这女的
I can't stand that woman.
啊? 我还以为你喜欢她
What? I thought you liked her.
你以为我们喜欢什么?
What did you think we liked?
她在公众场合和你舌了一大堆的吻?
The bizarre amount of time she French-kissed you in public?
或者一直说犹太话？
- 这可是榜上有名的反犹太行为 - 这女孩真的很
- on the anti-semitic. - That girl is so...
- 嘿 我忘了钱包 - 嘿
- Hey! Forgot my purse. - Hey.
我们应该给你装个铃铛
We're gonna have to put a bell on you.
噢! 叮 叮 叮 过来
Oh! Ding, ding, ding. Come here.
我以为是在帮你个mitzvah
But I thought it was doing you a mitzvah.
你犹太话还没说够吗
Enough with the yiddish.
好 这件还是这件?
Okay, this one or this one?
知道吗? 我觉得你该穿裤子
You know what? I think you should wear pants.
这样你踢正步的时候就方便多了
You know? It'll give you more freedom to goose-step.
我可不觉得那样很好笑
I can't find that funny.
噢 别这样
Oh, come on.
我为这个谈话还专门查了"二战"的喂鸡百科呢
I wiki'd "World War II" just for this conversation.
那你和 希特勒 今晚要做什么?
So what are you and Hitler gonna do tonight?
看电影? 吃饭? 入侵波兰?
Movie? Dinner? Invade Poland?
你说完没?
Are you done?
还有一句 我希望他是你的真命天子
I got one more. I hope he's Mr. Reich.
不错，等的就是这句
Glad we waited for that one.
你觉得我和他出去疯了吗?
Do you think I'm crazy, going out with him?
我是说 如果我和他结婚
I mean, if we got married,
那么 这就是我的未来
okay, this is my future...
彭妮 希特勒 道格 和 彭妮 希特勒
Penny Hitler, Doug and Penny Hitler.
道格拉斯 希特勒 夫妇?
Mr. and Mrs. Douglas Hitler?
噢 "道格拉斯" 有点帮助吧
Ooh, the "Douglas" helps a little.
听着 为什么你不就叫 "彭妮 哈茨"呢?
Look, why don't you just keep "Penny Hartz"?
或者用个连字符
Or you can hyphenate it.
彭妮 哈茨-希特勒
- Penny Hartz-Hitler.
是啊，好多了
Yeah, that's a winner.
别这样 如果那个人的姓氏
Come on. If this guy's last name
是他最差的东西 那也不算太坏
is the worst thing about him, that's not so bad.
我是说 他听上去也是个不错的人
I mean, he sounds like a pretty great guy.
知道吗 你是对的 完全正确!
You know, you're right. You are right!
名字有什么关系呢?
What does a name even matter?
我说 谁会在乎呢 是吧?
I mean, who cares, right?
我和那个土耳其人 阿尼德 几内次也约会过
I dated that turkish guy, Ahneed Jirnutz.
噢 我喜欢他
Oh, I liked A.J.
那出什么问题了?
What went wrong with that?
嘿 马科斯
Hey, Max.
是阿莱克斯吗 或者是女雕塑家拉丽莎
Is this Alex, or is this Larissa the sculptress
拥有这个迷人的声音?
with the sultry voice?
- 简 呢? - 她沉船了
- What happened to Jane? - She tanked.
你是对的 拜托 我这次真的很需要你的帮助
You were right. Please, Al. I really need your help on this.
那才是我想听的
That's all I needed to hear.
把细节告诉我 Larissa马上就到
Just give me the deets, and Larissa is on her way.
8:30 好了
8:30, okay..
非常感谢 呃 还能请你帮个忙吗?
Thank you so much Oh, could you do me a favor?
不要太刻意的弄些犹太的东西
Go easy on the Jewish stuff.
简 试过 可是都不买账
Jane tried it... not well received.
明白
Got it.
我要成为MAX的假女友了
I am gonna be Max's beard.
你愿意帮他还真是奇怪
So weird you wanna do that.
祝你和 希特勒 今晚过得愉快
Have fun with Hitler tonight.
小心别让他对你开“炮” 嘣!
Make sure he doesn't get in your panzer. What? Boom!
老兄 你为啥还有找其他人?
Dude, why do you need another beard?
你父母已经认为你是个异性恋了
Your parents already think you're straight.
是啊 我妈是犹太人
Yeah, my mom is Jewish.
要是我不快点找个她喜欢的姑娘
If I don't find a girl that she likes soon,
她就会替我在她的所有朋友中
she's gonna start setting me up
找个 "风趣" 单身的女孩
with all her friends' "fun" single daughters.
那你为什么不直接出柜?
Then why not just come out?
我是说 你父母知道我是同志也没什么啊
I mean, your parents are cool with me being gay.
你爸爸还一直告诉我他有多喜欢"妈妈咪呀"
Your dad can't stop telling me how much he loves "Mamma Mia."
呃 可你不是他们的儿子 知道吗?
Well, you're not their son, Ok?
他们还要在这待 4 个小时
They're here for 4 more hours.
用这个方式最简单
It's just easier this way.
是吗? 但看上去还有很多事要做
Really? 'Cause it seems like a lot of work.
多事?你曾经和米里亚姆 谢克特的女儿
Work? You ever been on a 6-hour architectural tour
邱吉尔 有过 6 小时的建筑学旅行吗?
with Miriam Schecter's daughter Chuchel?
邱吉尔 谢克特 是犹太人?
Chuchel Schecter's Jewish?
表面上是
Only in the face.
他们怎么可以不喜欢我?
How could they not like me?
呃 我喜欢你 那就足够了
Well, I like you and that's all that matters.
- 我知道怎么回事了 - 又来了
- I know what happened. - Here we go.
我太过了，可能有点太粘人
I tried too hard. Probably came off a little needy.
我应该去向他们展示一个轻松随和的jane
I should go over there and show them easy, breezy Jane.
有这样的ane吗?
There's an easy, breezy Jane?
- 我该戴珍珠吗? - 别那么做
- Should I wear pearls? - Don't do this.
你是对的 很对 不该戴 应该保持简洁
You're right. You're right. No pearls. Keep it simple.
宝贝 你已经做了你该做的
Babe, you did your job.
他的父母认为他是直的了
His parents think he's straight.
别过去了 那不关你的事
Don't go over there. It's not about you.
你很对 那不关我的事
You're right. It's not about me.
现在我们上楼去
Now let's go upstairs.
为什么你脱掉那些东西?
Why don't you lose all of that?
喔
Whoa.
做一些关于你的事
And let's make it all about you.
好 关于我的事!
Okay. It's all about me!
现在什么时间? 做爱的时间
What time is it? Sex o'clock.
该死! 简? 别去
Damn it! Jane? Don't do...
啊!
aah!
- 嗨 -  嘿 进来
- Hi. - Hey. Come on in.
- 谢谢 喔 你看上去真美 - 呃 谢谢
- Thank you. Wow, you look great. - Oh, thank you.
呃 彭妮 我真的很高兴你能接受我的邀请
So, Penny, I am really glad you decided to go out with me.
我也是 我昨天很蠢 我很真诚的说
Me, too. It was silly. I-I really honestly...
对你的名字我没什么不满
I don't have a problem with your name.
事实上 我很喜欢 道格 希特勒
In fact, I kinda like it. Doug Hitler.
我去拿包 我就要和 希特勒 约会了
I'm gonna go grab my bag 'cause I'm going on a date with Hitler.
- 听上去不错吧 希特勒? - 呃 是的
- Sound good to you, Hitler? - Uh, sure.
希特勒 希特勒 希特勒
Hitler, Hitler, Hitler.
我为今晚的可爱的约会预约了 呃
So I made us a reservation at this cute, little, uh...
怎么了?
Is there something wrong?
这是什么?
What's... this?
呃 什么也不是
Uh, nothing.
你对我着迷了吗 还是?
Are you obsessed with me or something?
什么?没有 呃
What? No. Unh-unh.
没有 我只是写着玩
No, no, I was just testing it out
看看我能不能用你的名字
to see if I could get on board with your name.
哦 呃 看上去你很能运用嘛
Oh, well, you seem a little too on board with it.
呃 我只是想想象一下
Yeah, I was just trying to imagine how it would be
- 将来会怎样 - 仅仅喝过一杯之后?
- in the future. - After one drink?
哦 我知道了
Oh. I see what this is.
你也是个那种希特勒怪胎
You're one of those Hitler freaks.
而我就是你最终值得纪念的事
And I'm the ultimate piece of memorabilia.
等等 什么啊?
Wait. What?
你们这些怪胎总是会找到我
You weirdos always find me.
所以 怎样 你想把我带到一些
So, what, you wanna take me
聚会 然后炫耀吗?
to some rally, show me off or something?
不是的 好了 这不是看上去的那样
No, okay, this is not what it looks like.
老实说 我们重新开始好吗?
Honestly, can we just start fresh?
这是MAX让ALEX不要太刻意的弄犹太东西的时候，ALEX记下的。
在“犹太人”上面划一杠，可以理解为反犹太
不 这个我也不知道如何解释了
No. That's gonna be hard to explain.
是啊
Yeah.
阿莱克斯在哪? 她都迟到了 20 分钟了
Where is Alex? She's, like, 20 minutes late.
这样更好 知道吗?
It's better this way, you know?
这可以是你的出柜晚餐
This dinner can be about you coming out
同时也是我的“入柜”晚餐（即澄清他是直男）
and me coming in.
马科斯 亲爱的 我们想和你谈谈
Max, darling, wanna talk to you a minute.
呃 马科斯  亲爱的
So, Maxie, honey,
我知道准确的说你还和 简 在一起
I know that technically you're still with Jane,
但巴里 恰克尼克 的侄女凯莉 恰克尼克
but Barry Schkolnick's niece Carrie Schkolnick,
刚刚从布兰德斯毕业 她想找一个人
just graduated Brandeis and is looking for someone
带她到处转转
to show her around.
只是作为朋友 但后面的谁知道呢?
Just as friends. But who knows?
哦 谢谢 戴夫 你的下杯水果汁我请
Ooh, thanks, Dave. Your next daiquiri is on me.
谢谢 别那样
Thanks. Stop that.
马科斯 你不是有事要告诉他们吗?
Max, don't you have something you wanna tell them?
呃 是的 我确实有事要告诉你们
Uh... yeah, I do have something to tell you...
葆琳 霍华德你们再给我次机会
Pauline, Howard, you need to give me a second chance.
-你们该再给简一次机会 我爱她 -马科斯
- You gotta give Jane a second chance. I'm in love with her. - Max.
听着 简 你会把事情搞得更糟...
Look, Jane, you're only gonna make things wor...
老兄!搞毛啊 伙计?
Dude! What the freak, man?
把脸从我老婆脸上拿开
Stop sucking my wife's face.
你结婚了?
You're married?
你怎么可以? 这个男的是谁?
How could you? Who is this man?
马科斯
Max.
好吧 我没有和简恋爱 我说谎了
All right, I'm not in love with Jane. That was a lie.
但事实是 呃 这真的很难说
But the truth is... It's... it's kinda hard to say.
为什么 亲爱的? 怎么会很难说?
Why, sweetie? What could be so hard?
朋友们 宝贝 对不起我迟到了
Guys, babe, I am so sorry I'm late.
- 我的雕塑有些问题 - 这是我的新女友
- I had a problem sculptressing. - This is my new girlfriend.
- 马科斯 - 你叫 阿莱克斯 来?
- Max. - You called Alex?
谁是阿莱克斯? 我是拉丽莎
Who's Alex? I'm Larissa.
阿莱克斯
Alex.
这是阿莱克斯 那个甩了你的阿莱克斯 ?
This is Alex... the Alex who left you?
是的
- Yes.
所以你对你已经结了婚的女友出轨
So you're cheating on your married girlfriend
然后和你最好朋友的前未婚妻搞在一起
with your best friend's ex-fiancée
那就是她离开他的原因?
that's why she left him?
还有因为他是同志
Well, and also 'cause he's gay.
天 这太奇怪了 知道吗 马科斯
Oh, this is so strange. You know, Max,
应该和那个 彭妮 在一起
you should have stayed with that Penny.
她人很好 也很正常
She was a nice, normal girl.
嘿 朋友们 知道吗?
Hey, guys, guess what?
我终于决定不和 希特勒 一起了
I finally decide I'm into Hitler,
结果对他来说，我还纳粹的过头了
and it turns out I'm too much of a Nazi for him.
什么?
What?
噢 嘿 布鲁先生和太太
Oh, hey, Mr. and Mrs. Blum.
两个荡妇 还有纳粹?
Two sluts and a Nazi?
你到底喜欢什么 马科斯?
What are you into, Max?
老爷儿们
Uh, dudes.
- 其实我喜欢男的 - 他说啥?
- I'm into guys. - What did he say?
我是同志
I'm gay.
你是同志?
You're... You're gay?
哦
Ohh.
是的 我本来想早点说的
Yeah, I-I... I wanted to tell you sooner.
我只是不知道你们会有什么反应
I just... I didn't know how you were gonna react,
而且我很害怕
and I... I was scared.
所以
So...
你没有和这些女的约会
You're not dating any of these women.
没有
I'm not, no.
- 噢 谢天谢地 - 松了一口气
- Oh, thank God. - What a relief.
- 哦 太好了 - 好了
- Oh, what a relief. - Okay.
什么? 你们不失落吗?
What? You're not upset?
亲爱的 你永远都不用害怕告诉我们任何事情
Sweetheart, you never need to be scared to tell us anything.
对我们来说最重要的是你幸福就好
What matters to us is that you're happy
还有你的身边有一群爱你的人
and that you're surrounded by people who love you.
我爱你 马科斯
And I love you, Max.
我很抱歉我是个糟糕的同志女友
I'm so sorry I was such a terrible beard.
我也不说谎了 你糟透了
I'm not gonna lie. You sucked.
但你还是帮了我很大的忙 谢谢
But you did get me here, so thank you.
- 到这来 亲爱的 - 哦!
- Come here, tataleh. - Ohh!
- 不是你 - 好吧
- Not you. - All right.
是你
You.
哦
Aw.
- 哦 - 耶
- Aw. - Yay.
早跟你们说了出柜会很GAY
I told you coming out would be gay.
你知道谁也是同志吗 罗达 卡普兰的儿子
Oh, you know who's gay, is Rhoda Kaplan's son.
而且他还有间迪斯科舞厅
And he owns a Discotheque.
噢 还有 厄玛 夏菲尔的儿子也出柜了
Oh, and Irma Schaefer's son just came out.
他有三个孩子 霍华德 我们就要有孙子了
He has three kids. Howie, we'd have grandchildren.
事实上，他名花有主了
Actually, he's spoken for.
我就知道
I knew it.
哦!
Aw!
我很感激你做的
I appreciate what you're doing,
不过你不是我的菜
but you're not my type.
哦 哦 恩
Aw. Aw. Mm.
我们评估了你的申请
So we reviewed your application.
看起来你们很适合格林考斯乡村俱乐部
It seems like you're perfect for Glenoaks Country Club,
威廉姆斯先生和太太
Mr. and Mrs. Williams.
拜托 叫我 布拉德福德
Please, call me Bradford,
- 叫她呆萌小妞，是吧？ - 真有趣
- and call her intellectually inferior, am I right? - That's funny.
呃 布拉德福德 你的申请上说
Uh, Bradford, your application says
- 你喜欢扬帆航行 - 我不是喜欢而是爱
- you like to sail. - I don't like it, sir. I love it.
- 恩 - 大海的微风吹过我的胸毛
- Mm. - The sea breeze flowing through my chest hair.
- 是的 - 我双脚赤裸的站在甲板上
- All right. - The way my bare feet feel on the deck.
- 恩 - 海鸥在头顶飞过 用它们的语言
- Mm-hmm. - The seagulls whizzing by and speaking to one another,
- 对彼此诉说 - 又要孩子气了
- in their bird language. - Getting immature. Getting immature.
- 嘎! 嘎 你! - 恩
- Caw! Caw you! - Mm.
- 嘎 嘿小妞! - 声音
- Caw you, girl! - Audio.
请告诉我 你停的是哪个码头?
So tell me, what Marina do you dock in?
恩 呃
Um, well... the...
亲爱的 那有个
Honey, the... there's the...
- 丹尼斯 码头 - 丹...尼斯
- the Dennis marina. - De... nnis.
事实上是由 丹尼斯 弗兰兹 建立的
That was founded by... Dennis Franz, actually,
在一个很怪的拐角那
in a weird twist.
- 恩哼 - 喔
- Mm-hmm. - Wow.
看看这些 哈? 来了
Get a load of these, huh? Oh, here we go.
就是这个
There they are.
你会留下我们的申请吗?
So... You'll keep us on file?